O	0	1	[
O	1	6	Tease
O	6	7	]

O	9	22	CONGRESSIONAL
O	23	30	WITNESS
O	30	31	:
O	32	33	I
O	33	34	`
O	34	36	ve
O	37	43	worked
O	44	47	all
O	48	50	my
O	51	55	life
O	55	56	,
O	57	60	and
O	61	62	I
O	63	68	never
O	69	76	thought
O	77	78	I
O	79	84	would
O	85	89	ever
O	90	94	have
O	95	97	to
O	98	101	ask
O	102	105	for
O	106	110	help
O	111	115	like
O	116	120	this
O	120	121	.

O	122	128	Before
O	129	133	this
O	134	135	I
O	136	141	tried
O	142	144	to
O	145	149	work
O	150	153	two
O	154	158	jobs
O	159	160	`
O	160	163	til
O	164	165	I
O	166	169	was
O	170	174	down
O	175	177	to
O	178	182	skin
O	183	186	and
O	187	192	bones
O	192	193	.

O	194	196	If
O	197	198	I
O	199	202	had
O	203	206	any
O	207	213	choice
O	213	214	.

O	215	216	I
O	217	222	would
O	223	227	have
O	228	229	[
O	229	234	never
O	234	235	]
O	236	240	even
O	241	248	applied
O	249	252	for
O	253	257	food
O	258	264	stamps
O	264	265	.

O	266	269	But
O	270	271	I
O	272	275	don
O	275	276	`
O	276	277	t
O	278	282	have
O	283	284	a
O	285	291	choice
O	291	292	.

O	293	300	Without
O	301	305	food
O	306	312	stamps
O	312	313	.

O	314	315	I
O	316	322	simply
O	323	328	could
O	329	332	not
O	333	337	feed
O	338	340	my
O	341	347	family
O	347	348	.

O	350	351	[
O	351	357	Titles
O	357	358	]

B-person	360	366	ROBERT
I-person	367	374	MacNEIL
O	374	375	:
O	376	380	Good
O	381	388	evening
O	388	389	.

B-person	390	399	President
I-person	400	406	Reagan
O	407	411	goes
O	412	418	before
O	419	420	a
O	421	426	joint
O	427	434	session
O	435	437	of
B-organization	438	446	Congress
O	447	451	this
O	452	459	evening
O	460	462	to
O	463	467	seek
O	468	475	support
O	476	479	for
O	480	483	his
O	484	492	economic
O	493	500	program
O	500	501	.

O	502	505	And
O	506	511	while
O	512	517	there
O	518	525	appears
O	526	528	to
O	529	531	be
O	532	533	a
O	534	541	growing
O	542	551	political
O	552	561	consensus
O	562	568	around
O	569	572	the
O	573	582	President
O	582	583	`
O	583	584	s
O	585	593	approach
O	593	594	,
O	595	599	some
O	600	602	of
O	603	606	his
O	607	615	proposed
O	616	622	budget
O	623	627	cuts
O	628	631	are
O	632	637	still
O	638	639	a
O	640	646	matter
O	647	649	of
O	650	656	bitter
O	657	663	debate
O	663	664	.

O	665	669	Some
O	670	672	of
O	673	676	the
O	677	684	loudest
O	685	693	protests
O	694	701	concern
O	702	706	food
O	707	713	stamps
O	713	714	,
O	715	717	an
O	718	719	$
O	719	720	1
O	721	722	l
O	722	723	-
O	723	730	billion
O	731	738	program
O	739	743	from
O	744	749	which
O	750	753	the
O	754	768	administration
O	769	774	wants
O	775	777	to
O	778	781	cut
O	782	788	nearly
O	789	790	$
O	790	791	2
O	792	799	billion
O	800	802	by
O	803	813	tightening
O	814	825	eligibility
O	825	826	,
O	827	830	and
O	831	842	eliminating
O	843	848	fraud
O	849	852	and
O	853	858	abuse
O	858	859	.

B-organization	860	863	The
I-organization	864	869	White
I-organization	870	875	House
O	876	885	maintains
O	886	890	that
O	891	894	the
O	895	904	genuinely
O	905	910	needy
O	911	915	will
O	916	919	not
O	920	922	be
O	923	927	hurt
O	927	928	,
O	929	932	and
O	933	937	that
O	938	944	losses
O	945	947	to
O	948	956	families
O	957	960	now
O	961	969	eligible
O	970	973	for
O	974	978	food
O	979	985	stamps
O	986	990	will
O	991	993	be
O	994	1000	offset
O	1001	1003	by
O	1004	1009	lower
O	1010	1015	taxes
O	1015	1016	.

B-organization	1017	1031	Administration
O	1032	1041	opponents
O	1042	1049	dispute
O	1050	1054	both
O	1055	1061	claims
O	1061	1062	.

O	1063	1066	The
O	1067	1073	debate
O	1074	1077	was
O	1078	1084	joined
O	1085	1090	today
O	1091	1093	in
B-organization	1094	1102	Congress
O	1103	1107	when
O	1108	1115	members
O	1116	1118	of
O	1119	1122	the
B-organization	1123	1128	House
I-organization	1129	1140	Agriculture
I-organization	1141	1153	Subcommittee
O	1154	1159	began
O	1160	1167	marking
O	1168	1170	up
O	1171	1175	food
O	1176	1181	stamp
O	1182	1193	legislation
O	1193	1194	.

O	1195	1202	Tonight
O	1202	1203	,
O	1204	1208	with
O	1209	1212	the
O	1213	1223	principals
O	1224	1226	of
O	1227	1231	that
O	1232	1238	debate
O	1238	1239	,
O	1240	1244	will
O	1245	1249	food
O	1250	1255	stamp
O	1256	1260	cuts
O	1261	1265	hurt
O	1266	1269	the
O	1270	1275	truly
O	1276	1281	needy
O	1281	1282	?

B-person	1283	1286	Jim
O	1286	1287	?
